A Guide to the Records of the Governor's Office, First Lady Anne Holton and Executive Mansion, 2002-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
Library of Virginia
- Series I. First Lady's Files, 2006-2009., Extent: 2.98 cu.ft. (boxes 1-9).
  - Subseries I.A. Public Event Files, 2006-2009., Extent: 1.93 cu. ft. (6 boxes)
    - Reading is Fundamental Gala, Washington, D.C., 2009 June 2. (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Middle School's 8th Grade Moving On Ceremony, Richmond, 2009 June 8. (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Summer Challenge Event, Binford Middle School, Richmond, 2009 June 9. (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Virginia Law Enforcement Torch Run Ceremony, State Capitol, 2009 June 12. (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Graduation and Founder's Day, Hanover Juvenile Correctional Center, 2009 June 12. (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - United We Serve Kick-Off, Shenandoah National Park, Luray, 2009 June 22. (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Zach Bonner Press Conference, Capitol Square, 2009 June 29. (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - SPARC Groundbreaking, Richmond, 2009 July 21. (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Children's Bureau 2009 Meeting of Agencies and Courts, Crystal City, 2009 August 6. (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - CenterStage Opening, Carpenter Center, Richmond, 2009 September 12. (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - CenterStage Ribbon Cutting and Performance, Richmond, 2009 September 12. (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Virginia is for Lovers, State Capitol, 2009 September 23. (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Richmond Bar Event, Second Presbyterian Church, 2009 September 23. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Groundbreaking Event, State Fair of Virginia, Doswell, 2009 September 24. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - National Summit on Marriage, Parenting and Families, Hampton, 2009 September 29. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Step Up for Kids Rally, Capitol Square, 2009 October 8. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Speak to Honors Class, VCU, Richmond, 2009 October 13. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Kids Press Event, Chamberlayne Elementary School, Richmond, 2009 October 13. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - AmeriCorps State Launch, Richmond, 2009 October 16. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Great Expectations Education Forum, Richmond, 2009 October 23. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Andy Block's Class, University of Virginia, Charlottesville, 2009 October 27. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - CHS Event, Richmond, 2009 November 5. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Sunshine Lady House for Mental Health Wellness and Recovery Dedication, Fredericksburg, 2009 November 5. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Beat the Odds Dinner, Washington, D.C., 2009 November 10. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - City of Richmond Adoption Day Celebration 2009 November 21. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Maggie Walker Governor's School National Honor Society Induction Ceremony, 2009 November 24. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Subseries I.B. Correspondence, 2006-2009., Extent: 1.05 cu. ft. (3 boxes)
    This Correspondence files are arranged chronologically by month. These records include acknowledgement letters, declined event invitations, thank you notes to/from First Lady Anne Holton and Asha Holloman, Director, Office of the First Lady.
    - 2006 January (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 2006 February (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 2006 March (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 2006 April (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 2006 May (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 2006 June (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 2006 July (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 2006 August (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 2006 September (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - 2006 October (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - 2006 November (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 2006 December (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - 2007 January (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - 2007 February (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - 2007 March (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - 2007 April (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - 2007 May (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - 2007 June (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 2007 July (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 2007 August (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - 2007 September (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - 2007 October (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - 2007 November (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - 2007 December (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - 2008 January (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - 2008 February (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - 2008 March (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - 2008 April (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 2008 May (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - 2008 June (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - 2008 July (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - 2008 August (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - 2008 September (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - 2008 October (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - 2008 November (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - 2008 December (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - 2009 February (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - 2009 March (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - 2009 April (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - 2009 May (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - 2009 June (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - 2009 July (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - 2009 August (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - 2009 September (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - 2009 October (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - First Lady Anne Holton's Initiatives, For Keeps-Families for All Virginia Teens, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Series II. Mansion Director's Files, 2002-2010., Extent: 1.40 cu.ft. (boxes 10-13).
  This series documents the activities and correspondence of the Amy Bridge, Executive Mansion Director, during the Mark Warner administration (2002-2006) and Tim Kaine administration (2006-2010). The files are roughly arranged by subject and/or date. These records include event invitations, invitation lists, event briefing forms, correspondence, photographs, invoices, and programs. Subjects include: Native American Tax Tribute Ceremony, holiday events at the Executive Mansion, Holiday cards from the Kaine family (2006-2007), information on the official portraits of Governor Mark Warner and Governor Tim Kaine and their unveiling, docent information, Commonwealth Dinners, visit of Queen Elizabeth II and photographs of select mansion events taken by Michaele White, Governor's Photographer, during the Warner and Kaine administration. Many of the event photographs may also be found in the Records of the Press Office's for Governor Warner and Governor Kaine.
  - American Indian Tax Tribute Ceremony, 2002 November 27. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - American Indian Tax Tribute Ceremony, 2003 November 26. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - American Indian Tax Tribute Ceremony, 2004 November 24. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - American Indian Tax Tribute Ceremony, 2005 November 23. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Executive Mansion Holiday Decorations, 2002. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Executive Mansion, Holiday Open House, 2002 December 7-8. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Capitol Tree Lighting Ceremony, 2002 December 11. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Executive Mansion Holiday Decorations, 2003. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Capitol Tree Lighting Ceremony, 2003 December 5. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Executive Mansion Holiday Decorations and Holiday Open House, 2004 December 4-5. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Executive Mansion Holiday Decorations, 2005. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Executive Mansion Holiday Decorations, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Executive Mansion Holiday Decorations, 2007. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Executive Mansion Holiday Decorations, 2008. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Executive Mansion Holiday Decorations, 2009. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Governor Mark Warner, Portrait Information, 2002-2006. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Governor Mark R. Warner Portrait Unveiling, Patrick Henry Building, 2006 May 16. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Governor Mark Warner Family Pets (dogs Buster and Beau) 2005. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence (Warner Administration, 2002-2004. (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Governor Tim Kaine, Portrait Information, 2008-2009. (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Governor Tim Kaine Portrait Unveiling, Library of Virginia, 2010 January 5. (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Kaine Family Photos, undated. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Governor Kaine Family Pet (dog Gina), undated. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Kaine Cabinet information, 2006. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Kaine Administration), 2006-2009. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Guest Chief (Kaitlin Payne), 2008. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Executive Mansion Docent Seminar, 2002 October 29. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Executive Mansion Docent Luncheon and Seminar, 2003 September 26. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Executive Mansion Docent Seminar and Luncheon, 2004 September 24. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Executive Mansion Docent Seminar and Luncheon, 2005 September 23. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Executive Mansion Docent Seminar and Luncheon, 2006 September 22. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Executive Mansion Docent Seminar and Luncheon, 2007 September 28. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Executive Mansion Docent Seminar and Luncheon, 2008 October 3. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Executive Mansion Docent Seminar and Luncheon, 2009 October 2. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Commonwealth Dinner, Executive Mansion, 2003 February 10. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Dinner for Virginia Supreme Court Justices, Executive Mansion, 2003 April 14. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Commonwealth Dinner, Executive Mansion, 2003 October 29. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Legislative Spouses Luncheon, Executive Mansion, 2004 February 27. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Commonwealth Dinner, Executive Mansion, 2004 May 7. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation Meeting and Luncheon, Executive Mansion, 2005 March 14. (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Dinner for the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Executive Mansion, 2005 May 16. (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Inaugural Open House, Executive Mansion, 2006 January 15. (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Event Binder, Official Visit of Her Majesty Queen Elizabeth II and His Royal Highness The Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh, 2007 May 3. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Copies of Invitation to reception for Queen Elizabeth II, Executive Mansion, 2007 May 3. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - NGA Management Seminar for Governors' Schedulers, Spouses' Assistants and Residence Managers, Richmond, 2007 June 11-13. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Awards for the Arts, Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Richmond, 2008 September 17. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Empherma-Business cards of Mark Warner, Tim Kaine and Anne Holton, undated. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Assorted Photos from Warner Administration, 2002-2005. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of American Indian Tax Tribute Ceremony, Executive Mansion, 2002 November 27. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Executive Mansion Holiday Decorations, 2002 December 5. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Holiday Photographs, Executive Mansion, 2002. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of Dinner for Chinese Ambassador, Executive Mansion, 2002. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of Commonwealth Dinner, Executive Mansion, 2003 February 10. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Executive Mansion Holiday Decorations, 2003 December 4. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of Commonwealth Dinner, Executive Mansion, 2004 May 7. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of Executive Mansion, Garden Week, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Series III. Mansion Events, 2006-2010., Extent: 1.05 cu.ft. (boxes 14-16).
  This series documents functions held at the Executive Mansion during the term of Governor Timothy M. Kaine (2006-2010). Arranged by date of event, the files contain invitations, invitation lists, event logistics, invoices, menus and schedule. Most events only contain invitation and/or guest lists.
  - Pilots Reception, 2006 January 4. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Politico Reception, 2006 January 4. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - PASS Program Reception, 2006 January 5. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Executive Mansion Open House, 2006 January 7. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Friends Reception, 2006 January 7. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - State of the Commonwealth Reception, 2006 January 11. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Breakfast, 2006 January 13. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - State of the Commonwealth Reception, 2006 January 16. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Transition and Inaugural Thank You Reception, 2006 January 17. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - New Legislator Reception, 2006 January 19. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Cabinet Dinner, 2006 January 23. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Public Information Officers, Reception, 2006 January 26. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - State of the Union Response, 2006 January 31. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - House of Delegates Reception, 2006 February 7. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - State Senate Reception, 2006 February 8. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Mixed Legislative Staff Reception, 2006 February 15. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - General Assembly Spouses brunch, 2006 February 24. (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - General Assembly Pages' Reception, 2006 March 1. (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation Meeting with Governor Kaine and Cabinet, 2006 March 27. (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Executive Mansion Dinner with Sir Freddy Ballantyne, 2006 April 4. (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Basketball Reception, 2006 April 19. (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - SWAM Reception, 2006 April 20. (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Jamestown 2007 Media Reception, 2006 April 24. (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Oliver Hill Reception, 2006 April 28. (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Jamestown 2007 Dinner, 2006 May 4. (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Governor Mark Warner Portrait Unveiling, Patrick Henry Building, 2006 May 16. (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Social Dinner, 2006 May 19. (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Virginia Military Advisory Council Reception, 2006 June 12. (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Community Integration for Virginians with Disabilities breakfast, 2006 June 22. (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Social Dinner, 2006 June 23. (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Governor's Fellows Dinner, 2006 July 11. (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Virginia, Maryland, and DC Meeting, 2006 July 14. (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - VEI Graduation Breakfast, 2006 July 28. (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Legislative Liaison Reception, 2006 August 21. (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Agency Head Reception, 2006 August 28. (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Money Committee Cookout, 2006 August 29. (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Fortune Magazine Reception, 2006 September 7. (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - University of Virginia's Men' Lacrosse Team Reception, 2006 September 14. (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - College Presidents' Dinner, 2006 September 25. (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Folklife Festival Reception, 2006 September 28. (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Virginia Economic Development Program, CEO Dinner, 2006 October 10. (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Virginia Supreme Court Dinner, 2006 November 2. (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - VEI Luncheon, 2006 November 3. (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - LEAD Breakfast, 2006 November 17. (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - American Indian Tax Tribute Ceremony, 2006 November 22. (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Staff Holiday Reception, 2006 December 4. (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Mansion and Executive Protection Unit Staff Reception, 2006 December 5. (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Foster Care Reception, 2006 December 12. (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Capitol Press Corps Reception, 2006 December 13. (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Department of Planning and Budget Reception, 2006 December 15. (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Cabinet Reception, 2007 January 5. (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Social Dinner, 2007 January 12. (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Foster Care Breakfast, 2007 January 15. (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - First Lady's For Keeps Press Conference, 2007 January 16. (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - School Superintendents Reception, 2007 January 16. (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - State Senate Reception, 2007 January 17. (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - House of Delegates Reception, 2007 January 18. (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - High Bridge Trail State Park Reception, 2007 January 31. (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation Meeting, 2007 February 12. (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - General Assembly Pages Reception, 2007 February 12. (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Richmond Ballet Breakfast, 2007 February 13. (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - General Assembly Spouses' Brunch and Tour, 2007 February 15. (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Legislative Assistants Reception, 2007 February 19. (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia Luncheon, 2007 March 6. (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Pilot's Dinner, 2007 March 12. (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Performance Evaluation Dinner, 2007 March 14. (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Project Corvette Breakfast, 2007 March 15. (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Capitol Square Civil Rights Memorial Foundation Reception, 2007 March 15. (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Oliver Hill Pre-Birthday Reception, 2007 March 25. (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Virginia Community College Luncheon, 2007 March 29. (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Royal Thank You Reception, 2007 May 17. (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - National Association of Women Judges Luncheon, 2007 May 19. (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - Reception for Senator John H. Chichester and Delegate Vincent F. Callahan, Jr., 2007 May 21. (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - Indian Delegation Reception, 2007 May 22. (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - CEO Dinner, 2007 May 23. (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - National Governors Association Seminar, 2007 June 11-13. (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - Staff Send Off Party, 2007 June 28. (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Social Dinner, 2007 June 29. (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - Social Dinner, 2007 July 14. (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - Bill Leighty's Retirement Party, 2007 July 11. (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - Fellows' Breakfast, 2007 July 18. (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - YRichmond Reception, 2007 July 26. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Oliver Hill Viewing, 2007 August 11. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Staff Picnic, Camp Pendleton, 2007 August 18. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Siegel/Farrar Wedding, 2007 September 15. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Economic Development Partnership Dinner, 2007 October 2. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Social Dinner, 2007 November 14. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - American Indian Tax Tribute Ceremony, 2007 November 21. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Capitol Tree Lighting Ceremony and Executive Mansion Holiday Decorations, 2007 November 30. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Executive Mansion, Holiday Open House, 2007 December 1. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - New Members of the Virginia House of Delegates Reception, 2007 November 28. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Virginia FREE Reception, 2007 December 3. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - New State Senate Member Breakfast, 2007 December 5. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts Dinner, 2007 December 7. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Foster Care Reception, 2007 December 11. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Social Dinner, 2007 December 14. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Capitol Press Corps Reception, 2007 December 18. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Staff Holiday Reception, 2007 December 20. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - State of the Commonwealth Address Reception, 2008 January 9. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Board of Education Breakfast, 2008 January 10. (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Council on Virginia's Future Reception, 2008 January 10. (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Virginia School Superintendents Reception, 2008 January 15. (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - McKinsey Donor Reception, 2008 January 16. (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - State Senate Reception, 2008 January 29. (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Spouses of Members of the Virginia General Assembly Brunch, 2008 January 30. (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Foster Care Reception, 2008 January 30. (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - House of Delegates Reception, 2008 January 31. (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Virginia's Congressional Delegation Meeting, 2008 February 4. (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Social Dinner, 2008 February 8. (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - SWaM Reception, 2008 February 13. (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Jamestown 2007 Reception, 2008 February 15. (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Putney Dinner, 2008 February 18. (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - General Assembly Staff Breakfast, 2008 February 21. (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - General Assembly Pages Reception, 2008 February 28. (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - GRP Results Reception, 2008 March 7. (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Virginia Economic Development Partnership Luncheon, 2008 March 27. (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Scottish Luncheon, 2008 April 3. (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Social Dinner, 2008 April 9. (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Housing Opportunities Made Equal (HOME) Reception, 2008 April 23. (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Agency Head Reception, 2008 May 12. (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Virginia Economic Development Partnership Dinner, 2008 May 14. (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Valentine Richmond History Center Patrons Reception, 2008 May 16. (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - For Keeps Legislative Breakfast, 2008 May 28. (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Civil Rights Memorial Breakfast, 2008 July 21. (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Governor's Fellows and Interns Reception, 2008 July 23. (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Social Dinner, 2008 July 31. (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - ICMA Breakfast, 2008 September 19. (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Social Dinner, 2008 October 4. (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Local Judges Reception, 2008 October 17. (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Budget Reception, 2008 October 21. (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Workforce Partnership Reception, 2008 October 24. (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Voice for Change Reception, 2008 November 16. (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Commerce and Trade Reception, 2008 November 19. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - American Indian Tax Tribute Ceremony, 2008 November 26. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Capitol Tree Lighting Ceremony and Executive Mansion Open House, 2008 December 5. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Holiday Open House, 2008 December 6. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - State Board of Elections Reception, 2008 December 9. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - CORE Reception, 2008 December 10. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Capitol Press Corps Reception, 2008 December 11. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Foster Care Reception, 2008 December 16. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Holiday Staff Reception, 2008 December 18. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - State of the Commonwealth Reception, 2009 January 14. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - House of Delegates Reception, 2009 January 26. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - State Senate Reception, 2009 January 27. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Social Dinner, 2009 February 5. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation Meeting, 2009 February 9. (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - British Ambassador Dinner, 2009 February 12. (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - University of Richmond Football Reception, 2009 February 16. (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - General Assembly Pages Reception, 2009 February 18. (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Spouses of Members of the Virginia General Assembly Luncheon 2009 February 24. (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Israeli Ambassador Dinner, 2009 March 8. (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Dinner with Trigiani Family, 2009 March 18. (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - YWCA Reception, 2009 April 1. (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Volunteer Awards Reception, 2009 April 15. (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Heroes in Health Care Reception, 2009 April 30. (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Dinner for U.S. Supreme Court Justice Sandra Day O'Connor, 2009 May 13. (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Workforce Council Reception, 2009 June 10. (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Cabinet Cookout, 2009 June 14. (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Social Dinner, 2009 June 16. (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - First Family Cookout, 2009 July 12. (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Governor's Fellows and Interns Breakfast, 2009 July 23. (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Social Dinner, 2009 August 31. (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Ballet Breakfast, 2009 October 20. (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Great Expectations VCCS Reception, 2009 October 22. (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Social Dinner, 2009 November 18. (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - College Presidents Reception, 2009 November 23. (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - American Indian Tax Tribute Ceremony, 2009 November 25. (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Capitol Tree Lighting Ceremony, 2009 December 4. (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - CAC-Art Fund Reception, 2009 December 7. (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Foster Care Reception, 2009 December 8. (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Capitol Press Corps Reception, 2009 December 8. (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Press Clippers Breakfast, 2009 December 17. (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Children's Transformation Reception, 2009 December 17. (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Bishops Dinner, 2009 December 17. (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Support Services Luncheon, 2010 January 4. (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Portrait Unveiling Reception, 2010 January 5. (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Virginia Tech Families Gathering, 2010 January 9. (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Staff Open House, 2010 January 10. (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - State of the Commonwealth Reception, 2010 January 13. (Box 16, Folder 47)